Guide to the Rosalyn Baxandall and Linda Gordon Research Files on Women's Liberation TAM.210
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Rosalyn Baxandall and Linda Gordon Research Files on Women's Liberation
1948-1999
1968-1979
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Baxandall, Rosalyn Fraad, 1939-
Gordon, Linda
TAM.210
7 Linear Feet (7 boxes)
The Rosalyn Baxandall and Linda Gordon Research Files on Women's Liberation contain the research files of feminist historians Rosalyn Baxandall and Linda Gordon. Baxandall and Gordon are the editors of America's Working Women: A Documentary History, 1600 to the Present as well as Dear Sisters: Dispatches from the Women's Liberation Movement. The collection consists largely of printed ephemera from a number of short-lived feminist groups based around the US. This includes broadsides, brochures, cartoons, fliers, newsletters, pamphlets, and other publications. There are also several topical files relating to abortion, African-Americans, beauty standards, gays and lesbians, the media, pornography, and work. While the material ranges in date from 1948-1999, the bulk documents the women's liberation movement of the late 1960s and through the 1970s.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Materials donated by Rosalyn Baxandall and Linda Gordon in 1998. The accession number associated with this gift is 1998.013.
Arrangement
Folders are arranged alphabetically by organization and/or subject.
Biographical Note
Feminist historians Rosalyn Fraad Baxandall (1939- ) and Linda Gordon (1940- ) met in 1971 at a women's liberation demonstration. They have been working together ever since. Both teach women's history, Baxandall at SUNY/ College at Old Westbury, and Gordon at New York University. Baxandall and Gordon are the editors of America's Working Women: A Documentary History, 1600 to the Present (1976, 1995) as well as Dear Sisters: Dispatches from the Women's Liberation Movement (2000).
Rosalyn Baxandall has been a feminist activist for over 40 years, especially engaged in child care and reproductive rights. She first got involved with the New York based New York Radical Women. Linda Gordon too has been active in the feminist struggle since the 1960s. She worked with the Boston area, socialist-feminist group, Bread and Roses.
Scope and Content Note
The Rosalyn Baxandall and Linda Gordon Research Files on Women's Liberation contain the research files of feminist historians Rosalyn Baxandall and Linda Gordon. Baxandall and Gordon are the editors of America's Working Women: A Documentary History, 1600 to the Present as well as Dear Sisters: Dispatches from the Women's Liberation Movement. The material in the files ranges in date from 1948-1999, but the bulk documents the women's liberation movement of the late 1960s and through the 1970s. The Collection contains primarily research files on organizations and subjects. The majority of the files consist of printed ephemera, including brochures, cartoons, fliers, pamphlets, and other publications, which document many short-lived feminist groups of the era. Many of the documents found throughout the files highlight the grass-roots nature of the women's liberation organizations, shown through numerous hand-drawn fliers and publication cover sheets. The collection contains documentation from groups around the US. Organizations such as the Boston-based Female Liberation/Cell 16 and Bread and Roses, New York City groups, New York Radical Women, the Feminists, and Redstockings, as well as west coast groups, Seattle Women's Liberation and the Berkeley-Oakland Women's Union have materials in the collection. Topical files show Baxandall's and Gordon's interest in among other topics, the intersection of race and gender in the women's liberation movement, with files on African-Americans and civil rights, the fight for access to legal and affordable abortion and birth control, as well as beauty standards, child-care, gays and lesbians, the media, pornography, sterilization, and work. There are also a number of files from some of the early women's liberation conferences, both on the radical feminist side (Lake Villa, IL) and the socialist-feminist side (Ohio). A number of the documents in the collection were found and photocopied at other repositories, notably the Schlesinger and Duke Libraries.
Separated Materials
Irene Peslikis Cartoons (Seven cartoons about Reproductive Rights) have been separated and transferred to the Library's Non Print Collection.
Reproductive rights -- United States; Lesbians -- United States; Abortion -- United States.; Gay rights -- United States.; Group relations training.; Socialist feminism.; African Americans -- Civil rights.; Women -- Employment -- United States.; Feminism -- United States.; Feminists -- United States.; Cell 16 (Organization); Female Liberation, Inc.; Committee for Abortion Rights and Against Sterilization Abuse (New York, N.Y.); New York Radical Feminists; Redstockings, Inc.; Bread & Roses (Organization); Chicago Women's Liberation Union
- Abortion: Feminist Papers, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abortion: Practical Information, 1972-1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abortion: Protests, Legal Rights, 1968-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Abortion: Songs, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- African-American Events, 1971-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- African-American Feminist Theory, circa 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- African-American Feminist Theory, 1970-1977 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- African-American Marxist Women Activists, 1948-1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- African-American Poetry, circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- African-American Women, 1968- circa 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- African-American Women and Reproductive Rights, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- African-Americans and Work-Related Issues, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Alternative Households, circa 1970-1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Amazon Quarterly: A Lesbian-Feminist Arts Journal (Oakland, CA), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Anti-Abortion Movement, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Anti-War Activism, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Asian Women in the US, 1983-1989 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Association of Libertarian Feminists (New York, NY), 1979 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Autobiography, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Back-to-the-Land Movement, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Bay Area Women's Liberation: Tooth and Nail, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Beauty Pageants, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Bell Telephone Company, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Berkeley-Oakland Women's Union, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Bibliographies and Publications (various), 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Bibliographies on Women's Issues, 1970-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Birth Control, 1969-1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Black Panther Party, 1968-1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Boston Women's Collective: Women's Yellow Pages, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Boston Women's Movement: Position Papers, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Bread and Roses (Boston; Cambridge, MA), 1970 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Cambridge Arts Council: From Hearing My Mother Talk: Stories of Cambridge Women, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Canada, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Caucuses, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Chicago Women's Liberation Union, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Chicago Women's Liberation Union: Education and Social Services, 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Chicago Women's Liberation Union: Womankind, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Chicana Organizations in the US, circa 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Childbirth, 1977-1998 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Children's Books, Feminist Critiques of, 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Chile, circa 1976 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Civil Rights Movement, circa 1968 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Class and Caste, circa 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Colleges, 1968-1970 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Committee for Abortion Rights and Against Sterilization Abuse: CARASA News, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Committee for Abortion Rights and Against Sterilization Abuse: CARASA News, 1977-1982 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Conclusion, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Conference of Feminist Film and Video Organizations (New York, NY), 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Congress to Unite Women, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Consciousness Raising Methods and Organization, 1970-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Consumerism, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Cooperatives, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Coyote: Newsletter (prostitution), circa 1973-1979 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Crafts and Needle Work, 1970-1984 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Cuba, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Culture, 1968, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Dallas Area Women's Liberation: Newsletter, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Day Care Problems, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Day Care: Theoretical Problems and Reports, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Dayton Women's Liberation, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Demonstrations, 1969-1989 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- East Africa, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Eating Disorders, 1974-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Education, circa 1970-1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Education: Papers, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Environmentalists, circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- European Women's Liberation Movement, circa 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Families, circa 1971 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Family, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Federal Bureau of Investigation and the Women's Movement, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Female Liberation and Cell 16 (Boston; Cambridge, MA), 1968-1971 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Female Liberation and Cell 16 (Boston; Cambridge, MA), 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Feminism and Marxism, circa 1970 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Feminism, Mainstream Media Reactions to, 1968-1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Feminism, Older Women's Organizations Influenced by, 1970s (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Feminism, Women's Organizations Influenced by, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Feminist Anarchists, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Feminist Book Club, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Feminist Book Printing, circa 1977 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Feminist Cartoons, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Feminist Consciousness Raising, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Feminist Critiques of the Left, 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Feminist Graphics, 1970-1995 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Feminist Magazines (various), 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Feminist Media Critique, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Feminist Party, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Feminist Press: District of Organizing Drive, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Feminist Press Publications, circa 1972-1977 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Feminist Radio, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Feminists, the (New York, NY), 1969-1970s (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Forfreedom, Ann, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Fourth World Manifesto, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Friends of Facing Reality Publications (Detroit, MI), undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Friendship Among Women, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Furies, the: Lesbian/ Feminist Monthly (Washington DC), 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Garcia, Inez Case (San Francisco Bay Area), 1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Gay Activist Alliance (Miami, FL), 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Gay Autobiography and Vision, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Gay Liberation and Heterosexism, 1970s and 1980s (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Gays and Lesbians in the Workplace, circa 1974 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Gays and Lesbians Internationally, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- "Give to Tamiment" (as marked on original folder), circa 1970s (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Good-Bye to All That (Austin, TX) (lesbian organization), 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Great Britain, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Headpieces, General Statistics for, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Health, undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Health Industry, Criticism of, 1969-1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Health: Women of Color, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Heterosexuality, circa 1971-1975 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- High School, circa 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Hospital Workers, circa 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Houston International Conference, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
- International Women's Day: Pamphlets, Flyers, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Internationalism, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Jeanette Rankin Brigade, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Jeanette Rankin Brigade, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Jewish Women, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Johnson, Rebecca (New Mexico), 1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Jordan, Joan (Vilma Sanchez), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Journal of Liberation, a: Strategies for Organization, 1970-1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Kansas City Women's Liberation Union, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Know, Inc. (Pittsburgh, PA), circa 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Labor Interviews, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Labor Pains Newsletter (Cambridge, MA), 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Labour Protective Legislation, 1970-1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Language, circa 1970-1976 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Latinas in the US, circa 1977 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Laura X Archives, circa 1974-1995 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Left, 1970s (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Legal Defense Against Sex-Related Abuse, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Lesbian Beauty/ Dress, circa 1973 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Lesbian Bibliographies and Organizations, 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Lesbian Coming-Out, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Lesbian Feminism, circa 1972 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Lesbian Politics, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Lesbian Relationship, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Lesbian Theory and Autobiographical Texts, 1969-1996 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Lesbian Writing, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Lesbians and Class Critique, 1972-1977 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Lesbians and Gays in the Media, 1971-1978 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Lesbians and Motherhood, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Lesbians: Law, Discrimination, Violence, 1973-1978 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Lesbians of Color, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Liberal Feminism, 1968-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Liberation, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Lucy Parson's Women's Coalition (Boston, MA), 1970s (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Magazine of the Appalachian South, the: Women's Issue (VA), 1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- March for Women's Equality, 1972-1988 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Marriage and Divorce, 1966-1975 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Married Feminism, circa 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Marxist Family Theory, circa 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Marxist-Leninist Groups, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- McEldowney Carol: Personal Reflections, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Midwest Academy, the (Chicago, IL), 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Militants, circa 1975 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Miss America, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Motherhood, 1970-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Motive (New York, NY), 1969, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Mushroom Effect: A Directory of Women's Liberation (CA), circa 1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- National Conference Lake Villa (IL), circa 1968 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- National Conference of Neighborhood Women (New York, NY), 1970s (Box 4, Folder 18)
- National Socialist Feminist Conference (Ohio), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Native Americans, circa 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- New American Movement, circa 1974 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- New Haven Women's Liberation: Sister (monthly newsletter), 1970s (Box 4, Folder 22)
- New Haven Women's Publications, 1969-1970s (Box 4, Folder 23)
- New Left, 1967-1975 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- New University Conference, 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- New York Radical Feminists (New York, NY), circa 1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- New York Radical Women (New York, NY), circa 1968 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- New York Women's Liberation Center (New York, NY), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- News and Letters Women's Liberation Committee, circa 1970 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Newcomb College Archives: Center for Research on Women, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Non-Sexist Child Rearing, 1969-1976 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Off Our Backs (Washington DC), 1970 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Oregon Women's Land, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Organizations, 1970s (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Origins, circa 1960s (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Pamphlets (feminist) (Midwestern states), 1970s (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Pennsylvania National Organization for Women, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Peslikis, Irene: Cartoons and Correspondence, 1969-1995 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Poetry, circa 1970-1995 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Pointblank Times (Houston, TX), 1976 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Police Repression and Co-option of Women's Movement, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Politics of Childcare, 1969-1977 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Politics of Orgasm, 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Pornography, 1976-circa 1995 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Pregnancy and Birth, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Prison, Women in, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Prostitution, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Protest Against Mass Mobilization, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Psychiatry/ Counseling, circa 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Psychology, 1972-1976 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Quizzes (Humour), 1970-circa 1971 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Racism in the Women's Movement, circa 1969 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Radical Feminism, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Radical Women Conference: Discussion Draft (submitted by Clara Fraser), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Real Women: Newsletter (St. Louis, MO), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Redstockings (New York, NY), 1968-1970s, 1990s (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Redstockings (New York, NY), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Redstockings of the Women's Liberation Movement (New York, NY), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Reproductive Rights, 1969, 1977, undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Reproductive Technologies, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Republican National Convention: Miami Conventions Coalition Protest, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Research Group One: Research Group One Report No. 13: Women and Men, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Revolutionary Child-Rearing, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Rock Groups, circa 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Sagaris: Women's School, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Scene (Northridge, CA), 1975 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Science and the Oppression of Women, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Seattle Women's Liberation (Seattle, WA), 1968-1977 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Seifer, Nancy: Equal Rights and Working Class Women, circa 1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Self Defense, circa 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Self-Examination, circa 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Separatism, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Sex Discrimination in the Workplace, 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Sexual Diversity (celibacy, transsexuality), 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Sexual Harassment, circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Sexuality, 1968-1976 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Socialist Feminism, 1970-circa 1972 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Socialist Workers Party and Feminist Issues, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Sojourner Truth Organization, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Solanas, Valerie: SCUM Manifesto, circa 1971-1995 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Songs (texts), circa 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Southern California Library for Social Studies and Research: African-American Resources, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Spirituality, Feminist Writing on, 1971-1976 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Sports, 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Sterilization Abuse, 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Sterilization: Practical Information and Personal Stories, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Strikes, Women's Participation in, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Students for a Democratic Society, 1967- circa 1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Tax, Meredith, 1969-1996 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Technology, circa 1972 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Texan Woman, the (Austin, TX), 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Theatre Plays (texts), 1969-1977 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Theory, circa 1970s (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Tilting Soap (newsletter) (University of Texas Women's Center), 1978 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Toward a Radical Analysis of Women's Liberation (Providence, RI), undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Unbecoming Men (pamphlet), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Union W.A.G.E. (Women's Allegiance to Gain Equality), 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Unitarian Universalist Women's Federation (Boston, MA), 1969-1975 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- United Automobile Workers: Convention, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- United Automobile Workers: Oral History Interviews, circa 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Velvet Glove (Livermore, CA), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Violence, 1970s (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Violence Against Women, 1976-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Violence Against Women, 1971-1979 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Voice of the Women's Liberation Movement, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Wages for Housework, 1970-1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Waitresses, circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Washington D.C. Women's Liberation (Washington DC), 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- WEF Position Paper (health care), undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Welfare Activism, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- "Winds of Change" (radio play) (St. Louis, MO), 1976 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- W.I.T.C.H. (Chicago, IL/ New York, NY), 1970s (Box 6, Folder 17)
- W.I.T.C.H. (New York, NY), undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Woman's World (New York, NY), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Women: A Berkshire Feminist Journal (Lenox, MA), 1975 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Women: A Berkshire Feminist Journal (Lenox, MA), 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Women and Texas History: Archival Bibliography, undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Women in City Government United (New York, NY), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Women in the Armed Forces, 1973-1978 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Women in the Arts Foundation, Inc. (New York, NY), 1971-circa 1978 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Women of Youth Against War and Fascism: Battle Acts, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Women of Youth Against War and Fascism: Battle Acts, 1970-1972 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Women Office Workers, circa 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Women Strike for Peace (anti-Vietnam War organization), 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Women Workers, 1965-1973 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Women Workers Bibliography, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Women Workers' Job Experiences, circa 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Women Workers: Position Papers, 1970-1974 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Women Workers: Theory, circa 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Women's Businesses, circa 1974 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Women's Centers: Addresses, Calendars, Pamphlets, 1968-1975 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Women's Health, 1971-1978 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Women's Health Clinics, circa 1972-1996 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Women's International League for Peace and Freedom and Anti-Vietnam, 1960s and 1970s (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Women's Liberation and Anti-Imperialism, 1960s-1970s (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Women's Liberation and Men's Liberation, 1969-1977 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Women's Liberation and Women's Rights Movement, 1969-circa 1976 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Women's Liberation Center of Nassau County (New York), 1972 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Women's Liberation Institutions and Movement, Strategies for Building, 1968-1972 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Women's Liberation Movement, 1976-1990s (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Women's Liberation Movement Collections and Archives, 1980-1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Women's Liberation Newsletter (Boston, MA), 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Women's Liberation (New York, NY), undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Women's Liberation: San Francisco, 1970-1972 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Women's Liberation Seattle: And Ain't I a Woman? (newsletter), undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Women's Movement and Anti-Racism, circa 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Women's Movement, History of, circa 1971- circa 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Women's Movement in the South, 1967-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Women's Movement, Origins of, 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Women's Movement, Theory of/ History of, 1968-1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Women's National Abortion Action Coalition, 1971-1973 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Women's Occupational Health Resource Center, 1977-1980 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Women's Organizations and Electoral Politics, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Women's Organizations: Atlanta, 1969-1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Women's Organizations: California, 1972-1975 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Women's Organizations: Cleveland, 1970s (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Women's Organizations: Detroit, 1967-1970s (Box 7, Folder 21)